获取更多免费资源微信小程序【盘子巴士】
感谢普利策奖委员会
thank you, pulitzer committee,
授予我这等荣誉
for this joyous honor.
我的好朋友格洛丽亚·斯泰纳姆有一次问我
my good friend, gloria steinem, once asked me,
乔伊斯 你知道吗
"joyce, did you know that the magazine
普利策奖 1971年
你儿时在卧室里创刊的杂志
"you created in your childhood bedroom
会永远改变世界
would change the world forever?"
不 没有 我从来不敢想象
no. no, i never dared imagine--
把胸露出来
show me your tits!
给我看看你的胸
快啊宝贝儿
come on, baby!
奶子甩起来宝贝
shake them cans, baby.
对
yeah.
我想跟你讨论讨论 大庭广众之下
i'd love to discuss your use of catcalling
用骂人的方式跟女人交流的问题
to communicate with women on the street.
我相信当你在建筑业崭露头角的时候
i'm sure that this was acceptable
这样的行为是被接受的
when you were coming up in the construction industry,
但时代不同了
but times have changed.
所以如果你想认识我
so if you want to meet me,
可以跟我握手同时自我介绍
you can introduce yourself with a handshake and a name.
我是迈克
i'm mike.
我是乔伊斯
and i'm joyce.
很好 乔伊斯
cool, joyce.
那你要不要坐到我脸上来啊
so you gonna sit on my face or what?
洛杉矶会展中心
南加州杂志推介会
欢迎来到南加州杂志推介会
welcome to the southern california
未来的杂志创办者
magazine pitch festival, where we connect
与当今的出版商们
the magazine creators of tomorrow
南加州会展中心
签到处
在这里齐聚一堂
with the publishers of today.
今年参展的出版商们非常
this year's publishers are a fine--
可以不吸烟吗
do you mind?
哦 不好意思 他们规定
oh, i--i'm sorry. they got some policy
室内禁止吸烟
about smoking cigars inside,
搞得好像这里是他妈的医院一样
like it's a fucking hospital or some shit.
到你心仪的出版商处排起队吧
line up for whichever publishers float your boat.
用你三分钟的介绍来博得他们的青睐
dazzle 'em with your three- minute presentation,
嘿 这是你
hey, is that, uh-
第一次参加推介会吗
first pitch fest?
对 没错 所以我
yeah. yeah, so i'm just
想认真听她说的话
trying to listen to her.
我不想让你期望太高
i wouldn't get your hopes up.
-你说什么  -这里只是
- excuse me? - ah, it's just
随便什么人和妈妈桑们
that everybody and their mama's trying
来推销杂志的地方罢了
to sell a magazine nowadays.
就那种模仿《猫迷》杂志
for every, you know, "cat fancy"
《猫迷》杂志市北美非常有名的专为猫和猫主人打造的月刊杂志
说找到了自己的完美读者群
that finds its perfect niche audieence,
恨不得有一千多个叫名猫的杂志
there's about a thousand "cat-tastics"
将会崛起发达
that are gonna crash and burn, so.
谢谢你对蓬勃发展的杂志业做的回顾
thanks for the recap on the booming magazine industry.
我不是名猫 我也没模仿任何人
i'm not "cat-tastic" or any other imitator.
我的想法已经研究好几年了
i have been working on my idea for years.
-你说研究好几年了  -是的
- you say for years? - yeah.
很好 帮我个忙
good. do me a favor.
来跟我推介一下
come pitch it to me.
-你是个出版商  -是的
- you're a publisher? - i am.
咱们在里面见吧 好运
i'll see you in there. good luck.
道格·雷内蒂 出版商
底钱出版社
译者注：全是色情杂志名
《巨屌》《乳娘》
"giant juggs." "milky moms."
去放手一搏吧
now go forth and conquer!
谢兹曼出版社
我走路不摆臀
♪ i don't swing my hips when i walk ♪
我讲话不咬唇
♪ and i don't bite my tongue when i talk ♪
我不会任你摆布
♪ i don't move when you want me to move ♪
也不会俯首帖耳
♪ and i don't groove when you tell me to groove ♪
因为我是女王 永远都是
♪ cause i'm a queen, and i always will be ♪
你不妨来试试
♪ all you got to do is try me ♪
数学好难
"math is hard.
青春女孩
小说 娱乐 时尚以及好书推介
开学了让你觉得像呆瓜
when back to school makes you feel like a fool."
康泰纳仕
女孩
从约会到伴侣 你也可以嫁出去
"from date to mate: you too can snag a spouse."
西柚减肥法 轻松享瘦
"the grapefruit diet: find your thin within."
《女性自我》
这此文章有什么共同点呢
what do these articles have in common?
-可爱有趣  -都有美女照片
- they're cute and fun. - with pictures of pretty gals.
是我老婆会在泡澡时候看的那种读物
the kind of stuff my old lady reads in the tub.
他们的共同之处是 他们与我的杂志中要讲的故事
what they have in common is they're the exact opposite
截然不同 完全相反
of the stories i'm gonna have in my magazine.
这个国家对待女人犹如二等公民
this country treats women like second-class citizens.
女人们被忽视 薪酬过低 不堪重负
we're overlooked, underpaid, and overwhelmed.
女人们需要一个能激励我们
we deserve a magazine that inspires us--
告诉我们如何抗争的杂志
that shows us how to fight.
先生们 这是你们
gentlemen, this is your chance
可以站在历史正确面的机会
to be on the right side of history.
《女权觉醒》
"the matriarchy awakens."
自动化与
女性工人：
改变就在前方
监狱里的女性：
什么措施可以
帮助她们
婚内强奸：
当犯罪不被
视为犯罪
她为什么那么愤怒
why is she so angry?
我在之前的介绍里应该是讲到了的
uh, i believe i covered that in my presenta--
嘿 名猫
hey, "cat-tastic."
-需要帮忙吗  -不用我没事
- you need a hand? - no, i'm fine.
随便你吧
suit yourself.
你今天忘了来找我
hey, you forgot to find me today.
你进展如何
how'd it go?
我的推介稿需要再推敲一下
my pitch needs a smidge of work.
康泰纳仕是一个总部位于美国纽约市的国际期刊出版集团。包括《the newyorker》、《vogue》、《gq》、《vanity fair》、《conde nast traveler》、《wired》等知名杂志。该集团于1908年由康得·纳斯在美国创立。
是啊 你在康泰纳仕做推介的时候我听到几句
yeah, i overheard you at "conde nasty."
如果我是你 我就不会再吹嘘
hey, if it were me, i'd stop bragging
我跟那些最成功的女性杂志有多不同
about how different i was from the most successful
永远都不说这种话
women's magazines in, oh, i don't know, forever.
我会说我跟那些杂志很像
i would say that i was just like 'em, you know,
但是有区别
but--but with a twist.
对 也许这方法适合你
yeah, well, maybe that'd work on you,
但我要找的是不一样的出版商
but i'm looking for a different kind of publisher.
是吗 是哪种出版商呢
oh, yeah? and what kind is that?
找那种不迷恋
the kind that doesn't
哺乳期母亲的
fetishize lactating mothers.
嘴巴还挺毒
some mouth on you.
说出来让你参考下 我流动资金四百万
you know, for your information, i got 4 million
书架上有十二个奖项
in circulation, i got 12 titles on the rack--
是啊 一打色情业的奖项
yeah, a dozen pornography titles.
你觉得这些奖项很容易得到吗
what, you think that's easy to do?
乳房 更多乳房 哦看啊 更大的乳房
－ breasts, more breasts. oh, look--bigger breasts.
如果你必须做色情主题 至少做原创的
if you have to do porn, at least be original.
给老人拍裸照
photograph naked old people.
或者 做个全是裸男的杂志
or, i don't know, make a magazine full of nude men.
也许第一期的插页照片就用你本人的
you know what, maybe you could be the first centerfold.
看看你要是被物化了是什么滋味
see how you like being objectified for once.
你东西掉了
you dropped something.
我梦到我能飞
♪ yeah, i had a dream i could fly ♪
飞到高空中
♪ high up above the ground ♪
对不起亲爱的 我给忘了
i'm sorry, love, it slipped my mind.
我父母已经觉得你讨厌他们了
my parents already think you hate them.
我不讨厌你父母 格伦
i don't hate your parents, glenn.
讨厌他们给尼克松投票 可是
hate that they voted for nixon, but--
你知道我妈对这些假日派对有多投入
you know how my mom gets hung up on this holiday party.
这就是聪明女人不去工作的结果
well, that's what happens to smart women who don't work.
还拥有强大的脑子
still have these big brains,
只能用在不重要的事情上
so they use them on things that don't matter.
看 这就是个很好的选题
see, now that's a story idea.
对 当然是
right. of course it is.
-这是什么意思  -你的杂志 乔伊斯
- what does that mean? - your magazine, joyce.
咱们的恋爱关系是三人行
there are three people in this relationship,
不好玩的那种
and not in a fun way.
我知道我最近心不在焉的
look, i know i've been preoccupied lately.
最近吗 从咱们开始约会
lately? you've been completely obsessed
你就一直对杂志念念不忘
the entire time we've been dating.
那为什么现在才觉得不爽
well, then so why does it suddenly matter?
我本来以为你到这时候
i guess i just thought it would be out
差不多该翻篇了
of your system by now.
翻篇
out of my system?
你一直是在等着我
you've just been waiting for me to--
干嘛 放弃吗
what, give up?
乔伊斯
joyce.
我爱你
i love you.
杂志不会成的
the magazine's not working out,
我不明白你为什么还在坚持
and i don't get why you're still going.
你当然不明白了
no, of course you don't get it,
因为你写的那篇
because you rose through the ranks
关于千鸟格西装和窄翻领的文章
of a national magazine writing
在全国发行的杂志上脱颖而出
about houndstooth blazers and skinny lapels.
-好吧  -可我写的文章是政治性的
- okay. - but my stories are political.
没人想碰这种话题 所以我必须得自己做
no one wants to touch 'em, so i have to do it myself.
不 你不需要 把所有这些精力
no, you don't. just put all of that energy
投入到其他地方啊
into something else.
我们一起可以有很好的生活
we could have a great life together.
你是要让我选择吗
are you asking me to choose?
能选的也不多 对吧
well, it's not much of a choice, is it?
不 不是的
no, it's not.
如果你在水上行走
♪ if you walk upon the water ♪
脚开始沉入沙子
♪ your feet start sinking in the sand ♪
当分手是最佳选择
女人的世界
女权觉醒
父亲的时间 他必须放松
♪ father time, he must unwind ♪
有关女人的一切
性，女权主义
女人当权
诺尔目录
吸引力
静静心 放放空
♪ have a heart and lose his mind ♪
我相信咱们的背运将要改变
♪ i believe our bad luck is gonna change ♪
你好
hello?
是的 我情人节过的很开心
yes, i did have a good valentine's day.
我们有个情人节特惠活动
we actually have a valentine's day special.
今天下单可以打七折
30% off if you order today.
没错 每年只需要9美金
that's right, just $9 a year.
没错 关键位置就在这里
yeah, that's the sweet spot right there.
你应该试试给你男朋友按摩
you know, you should do this for your boyfriend,
让他爽歪歪
get him good and hot.
不好意思 您说什么
i'm sorry, what was that?
是的女士 任何时候都可以取消
yes, ma'am, you can cancel at any time.
下周就会收到第一份刊物
you'll get the first issue next week.
希望你的女儿喜欢
hope your daughter likes it.
如果像您说的她喜欢政治
if she's as political as you say, i'd recommend
我会建议您订阅新闻周刊
getting a "newsweek" subscription instead.
一场革命即将到来 而我们还在出版
there's a revolution coming, and we're still publishing
吹捧大卫·卡西迪的文章
puff pieces about david cassidy.
大卫·卡西迪 美国歌星，演员。70年代是其事业的巅峰，
据说那时候他的粉丝团人数比披头士组合和“猫王”的粉丝加起来还要多
嘿 亲爱的
hey ya, honey.
你怎么来了
what are you doing here?
我来绑架你的
oh, i came to kidnap you.
是你在你的杂志里写了你在哪里工作 傻瓜
nah, you put where you work in your magazine, dummy.
-你读了我的杂志  -是的
- you read my magazine? - i did.
怎么 你是以为我文盲吗
what, you think i'm illiterate or something?
-那个  -又不是《普劳斯特》
- well-- - look, it's not proust.
《普鲁斯特》作者是萨缪尔·贝克特（samuel beckett）
1969年因其作品“以新的小说和戏剧的形式从现代人的窘困中获得崇高”
而荣膺诺贝尔文学奖。
是《普鲁斯特》
it's pronounced "proost."
别人喜欢你吗
do people enjoy your company?
不太喜欢 你得赶紧离开 好吗
not really. look, you've got to go, okay?
我的同事都是正派人
my co-workers are g-rated.
她们穿针织套装带珍珠首饰
they wear sweater sets and pearls.
得了吧 那些穿毛衣的女孩
oh, come on, those sweater girls are all
内心都是怪胎 这一点你得信我的
freaks on the inside, you can trust me on that.
嘿 一点钟到莫特来
hey, come to mort's, 1:00.
咱们聊聊正事 好吗
let's talk business, okay?
你以为我会随随便便
you think i'm just gonna show up
为了什么神秘会面去跟人吃晚餐吗
for some mystery meeting in a diner,
好像我就没其他安排一样
like i have nothing better to--
我们之前在哈瓦苏湖
so, we're up in lake havasu,
给两个妞拍摄
and we're shooting these two chicks
《亚洲美臀》的封面
for the cover of "asian asses,"
我找到一个特性感的像越南稻田一样的角度
and i got this really sexy kind of vietnam rice paddy angle
结果负责化妆的小子 里奇 把一整袋胶片
and my makeup boy, richie, knocks the bag of film
掉进了水里
right into the water.
所以他去镇上的时候
so we got to shut down
我们只能收工
as he goes into town,
那两个妞就开始叽叽歪歪的
and the chicks start bitching, you know?
-她们是那样  -道格
－ they do that. - "doug, how long
还得等多久啊 外面好冷啊
is this gonna take? it's so cold out here."
你猜我怎么做的
so guess what i did.
重新思考你存在的意义吗
re- evaluated your entire existence?
我把车里有的唯一一本杂志
i gave them the only thing
给了她们
that i had to read in my car,
就是你的杂志
which was your magazine.
你的插页模特看了《女权觉醒》吗
your centerfolds read "the matriarchy awakens"?
她们也识字的
also not illiterate.
她们喜欢吗
did they like it?
也不是我关心 就是好奇她们是不是
not that it matters. i'm just curious if they--
她们都震惊了
it blew 'em away.
-真的  -真的
- it did? - it did.
已经三个星期了 她们还在讨论
it's been three weeks, and they're still
那些文章
talking about the articles.
其中一个女孩还来找我加薪
and one of em even hit me up
因为你写的一篇有关
about a raise because of something
薪酬差距的文章
that you wrote about the pay gap.
-这个  -虽然不可能
- well-- - i mean, she's not
给她加薪的
gonna get it.
我有很多男性读者
look, i got a lot of readers. men.
他们经常给我写信
and they write to me all the time,
告诉我 道格 世道变了
and they say, "doug, shit's changing."
女孩子也变了
you know, "chicks are changing."
所以我得弄清楚
so i got to figure out, you know,
怎么应对 下一步怎么办
what to do with that, what's next.
然后我开始思考
and then i started thinking
可能我不能再听男人的一家之言了
maybe i got to stop talking to the men.
我得去跟那此女人聊聊
maybe--maybe i should be talking to the women.
你想跟女性谈吗
you want to talk to women?
外面有很多像你这样的人
－ well, there's a lot of you out there,
我想分一杯羹
and i'd like a piece of that pie.
你该不会要发表
oh, you're not suggesting that you publish
《女权觉醒》吧
"the matriarchy awakens."
不会 天啊 才不会
oh, god no.
至少不能按照这个形式发行
i mean, not in its current form.
别误会 你的想法很好
hey, don't get me wrong, it's good.
但有个问题
it's just you got a challenge.
你的语气给人感觉太慷慨激昂了
and the tone, it comes across as shouty.
读起来有一种
when i'm reading it, i feel like
被班主任训斥的感觉
a fucking teacher is yelling at me.
谁在乎感觉啊
well, who cares how it makes you feel?
重点是让大家思考
it's supposed to make people think.
你需要把药藏起来
you got to hide the medicine.
就像喂狗吃药时
it's like when you give a pill to a dog,
要把药在花生酱沾一沽
you dip it in peanut butter first.
那么问题来了 我们的花生酱是什么
so my question is, what's our peanut butter?
-抱歉 你在等我回答  -是裸男
- i'm sorry, are you waiting-- - it's nude men.
你刚说裸男
did you say nude men?
不是那种肉欲横流的肌肉男
not like a schvantz right in the face,
你知道的 要优雅
you know, classy.
符合你们现代女性的审美
with your modern, you know, lady point of view.
你怕不是有什么大病
are you mentally ill?
别怪我啊 这是你最初的主意
you're the one who came up with the idea.
那就是一句客套话
no--that was a conversational bon mot.
你觉得我现在跟你坐在这里
do you even understand
是想干什么
what it is i am trying to do here?
我当然知道 你想要女权
of course, i do--feminism.
为女孩子们争取平等
making shit fair and equal for the chicks.
你倒是说说看 男人有一打
so tell me this, how is it fair and equal
能看女人奶子的地方 但女人一个看屌的地方找不到
that a guy has twelve places to go to see a pair of titties,
这算什么平等
but a gal has no place to go to see a dong?
女人不想看到屌
gals do not want to see a dong.
不想吗 你怎么知道
oh, they don't? now how do you know?
-因为我就是女的  -嗯
- because i am one, so. - mm.
好吧 你想花钱证明吗
well, would you like to put money on it?
-你是说赌一赌吗  -不是的 亲
- what, you mean, like a bet? - no, honey.
我是说办杂志
like a magazine.
他会为你提供办公室和一名员工
he wants to give you an office and a staff
并支持你发表前三期吗
and fund your first three issues?
你不是说这要花5万块吗
didn't you tell me that cost, like, 50 grand?
-也许吧  -乔西
- maybe. - joycie!
这可是一大笔钱
that's a lot of money.
对 但是有附加条件的
yeah, but it comes with strings.
你知道的 套路层层叠叠
you know, big ones wrapped around peckers.
也许藏在杂志背后的
maybe it'll just be a single, tiny weenus
只是一个小小的套路
hidden in the back of the magazine.
你干嘛要劝我干这个
why are you trying to talk me into this?
你是我的小妹
you're my baby sister.
我不想看你整天劳累奔波
i hate to see you spin your wheels.
你已经努力很久了
you've been at this for so iong.
我知道这是个好机会
look, i know it's a good opportunity.
-算是一个机会吧  -唯一的机会
- well, an opportunity. - the only opportunity.
但为什么偏偏是这个人呢
－ why does it have to come from this guy?
他错得太离谱
he's just so wrong.
你觉得莱尼具备我对
do you think that lenny had all of the qualities
一个丈夫的要求吗
i was looking for in a husband?
我想要的是一个喜欢到处旅行的人
you know i wanted someone who loved to travel,
而不是看一眼中餐都会拉肚子的人
not someone who gets diarrhea from looking at chinese food.
但他对我很好 他是个好爸爸
but he takes care of me. he's a great dad.
我虽然没得到期望中的一切
no, i didn't get everything i wanted, you know,
但我很知足
but i'm--i'm happy.
好吧 就算我愿意
－ all right, even if i wanted to,
你觉得这东西会有人接受吗
do you think i could pull this off?
这种程度上的裸体
the--the nudity?
怎么不会
why not?
因为我不是那种酷炫女生
'cause i'm not some sexy, cool girl.
-我上的是瓦萨学院  -对
- i went to vassar. - yeah, and that's what
这家伙就是看中这一点 想让七姐妹学院的人才
this guy wants from you, that seven sisters polish...
都来擦亮他的旋钮杂志
all over his magazine of knobs.
雪莉 你说得太恶心了
oh, shelly. don't be disgusting.
怎么了 你是色情作家
what? you're the pornographer.
你得习惯这种谈话
you got to get used to this kind of talk.
我是女人 听我咆哮吧
♪ i am woman, hear me roar, in numbers ♪
声音嘹亮 不容忽视
♪ too big to ignore - too big to ignore ♪
再不会有人让我失望
♪ no one's ever gonna keep me down again ♪
对 我很聪明
♪ oh, yes, i am wise ♪
但这智慧建立在痛苦之上
♪ but it's wisdom born of pain ♪
我已经付出了代价
♪ yes, i've paid the price ♪
但看一看
♪ but look how much ♪
我才得到多少
♪ i've gained ♪
不得已时
♪ if i have to ♪
我什么都可以做
♪ i can do anything ♪
我很坚强 坚强
♪ i am strong, strong ♪
我不可战胜 不可战胜
♪ i am invincible, invincible ♪
这里是罪恶之都吧
i'm in gomorrah.
需要帮忙吗
you need something?
早上好 你好
good morning. hello.
对 我是来见道格·雷内蒂的
um, yes, i'm here to see, um, doug renetti.
-我叫乔伊斯  -乔伊斯·普里格尔 是你吗
- my name is joyce-- - joyce prigger, is that you?
你好 我是斑比
hi! i'm bambi.
嗨 很高兴认识你
- hi-- - so good to meet you.
我是道格的模特
- hi. - i model for doug.
最近登上了《大块头》杂志
most recently in "bodacious butts."
我是五月 六月和七月小姐
i was miss may, june, and july.
是啊 哇哦 你这夏天够忙的
- oh--oh, wow. that's a busy summer.
对 都忙不过来了
yeah, it was almost too much.
其实挺累的
- oh. - i'm tired.
请允许我向你表达感谢
um, can i just say,
非常感谢你给我这个机会
thank you so much for this opportunity?
能向你这样的人学习我真的
i mean, to learn from someone like you is just--
道格没告诉你吗
oh, doug didn't tell you?
我为杂志社工作
i'm working for the magazine.
我是你的新插页协调员
i'm your new centerfold coordinator.
-是吗  -带你参观下
- oh! - okay, tour time.
什么是插页协调员
what is a centerfold coordinator?
不知道啦 是我瞎编的 听起来挺高大上的吧
i don't know, i made it up. doesn't it sound fancy?
我们这里跟普通的
okay, so it's basically just like
老办公室没什么不一样
any other regular old office.
有艺术部 编辑部
we have art department, editorial.
那边是运输部和会计部
that's shipping, accounting.
你不用担心格里
ugh. ignore gerry.
他就是生气而已 道格
he's just mad doug pulled the plug
毙掉了他的杂志 改做你的
on his magazine idea to do yours.
你们的会计都能创办杂志
your accountant created a magazine?
道格这个人你了解
yeah. you know doug.
他觉得任何人都有价值连城的好点子
he thinks a zillion-dollar idea can come from anyone.
这边是照片编辑和
this is all our photo editing and--
他在给那个女人的乳房涂胭脂吗
is he rouging that woman's breasts?
对的
oh, yeah.
强光下看不出乳房的粉色
um, nips don't read pink under hot lights,
我们必须
so we have to--huh.
里奇 小鸡鸡也要化妆的吗
richie, are we gonna have to put makeup on dicks?
但愿吧
mm, one can only hope.
那人是里奇
that's richie.
他是我们的化妆师
- oh. - he's our makeup artist,
也会是你的摄影师
but he's gonna be your photographer,
因为其他人都不想给鸡儿拍照
cause none of the other guys want to shoot wieners.
别担心 我知道怎么拍好看
don't worry, i know my way around a camera.
这么多年我一直在练习给我的伴侣拍照
i've been photographing my lovers throughout the years.
我喜欢你的套装
oh. ooh, i love this ensemble.
幸会
oh. enchante.
早啊
morning.
道格
doug.
看看谁来了
hey, look who made it.
你看起来很累 开了很久的车吧
you look beat. long drive?
来一杯咖啡怎么样
how's a cup of coffee?
来杯茶就好
a cup of tea would be divine.
呃 我不是秘书 我只是黑人
oh, i'm not the secretary. i'm just black.
很抱歉 我是因为看见
i'm so sorry. it was actually the way
你在倒水才以为
that you were pouring the waters that i thought that--
以为我是你网球俱乐部的服务生吗
reminded you of the help at your tennis club?
不 呃
- no. uh--ah, well,
我们确实是网球俱乐部的成员
we are members of a tennis club,
但是那里的服务生大多是墨西哥人
but the waitstaff there is mostly mexican, um--
她在逗你玩呢
she's fucking with you.
蒂娜就是我秘书 都当了十年了
tina's my secretary going on ten years.
-太好笑了  -种族歧视
- oh, that's very funny. - racist.
好了各位 这是我们的时间表 紧紧张张
all right, fuckers, here's our timeline, lean and mean.
只有一周时间做个试发期刊
a week to produce a test issue?
-这也太紧了  -要想做第一个吃螃蟹的人
- that is way too fast. - well, we got to boogie
就必须行动迅速 对吗
if we want to be the first out of the gate, right?
你是说还有别家也想发行
you think there's a second nude
女权主义裸体杂志吗
feminist magazine in the works?
就算现在没有 很快也会有
if there's not now, there soon will be.
插页创意 拍摄 大家有主意了吗
centerfold ideas, shoot. what do we got?
斑比 说吧
bambi, go ahead.
我在想
um, i was thinking,
女人觉得什么东西最性感
what's the number one thing women find sexy?
-智商  -摩托车
- intelligence-- - motorcycles.
想象一下 闪亮的哈雷摩托车
picture this: tricked out harley,
身材魁梧的肌肉男 油门上勾勒出鼓鼓囊囊的轮廓
big, muscley model with a juicy boner draped over the throttle.
标题是什么
- mm. - what's the caption?
-野猪  -油腻骑手
－ "wild hogs." - "greasy riders."
我知道了
- oh. - ooh, i got it.
加把劲儿 带我一骑绝尘
"rode hard and put away wet."
-对 不错  -这个好
- ooh, yes. - that's the one.
-斑比 真是绝了  -真的不错 斑比
- bambi, that's genius. - that's really good, bambi--
但这个
- yo--ah--this is just
和我想的不太一样
not quite what i had in mind.
不过第一次能这样也不错了
it's a great first try though.
-哪里不好  -只不过摩托车跟女权主义
－ what's wrong with it? - it's just, how do motorcycles
之间的联系
relate to feminism?
勃起符合我们的理念吗
are erections consistent with our philosophy?
如果我们的目标是在不同性别之间
if--if our goal is to level the playing field
建立公平的环境 为什么要把生殖器营造成
between the sexes, then should our penises
一种攻击状态呢
be ready to assault?
还是说它们应该平易近人 不显山露水
or--or should they be approachable and unassuming,
轻轻地搭在大腿上 被藏起来
draped gently on a thigh, tucked away, under a throw?
我想你没搞清楚中央插页的重点
i think you're missing the point of a centerfold.
没人关心什么理念
no one cares about philosophy.
唯一重要的问题是 它会让你性奋吗
the only question that matters is, does it turn you on?
这话题是老生常谈了
－ that is a question for the ages,
我们可以就此讨论好几个月
which we could debate for months.
我们也不想讨论几个月 对吧
well, we wouldn't want to do that, now would we?
我们也不想急于求成啊
well, we wouldn't want to rush into things either.
我们应该好好考虑
you know, we should give this magazine
这个杂志怎么做
the thought it deserves.
-我觉得是  -一些口碑很棒的
- and i think we are. - some highly
推荐书目
recommended reading,
《查特莱夫人的情人》
"lady chatterley's lover,"
还有《金赛性学报告》
and then we have the "kinsey report,"
第一卷和第二卷
volumes 1 and 2.
还有去年暑假的畅销书 《我们的身体 我们自己》
and last summer's bestseller, "our bodies, ourselves"
在93页有个关于外阴的章节 令人大开眼界
there is an eye-opening section on vulvas, page 93.
太好了
great.
你确定这一个吗 她好像有点小聪明
you sure about this one? she seems a little brainy.
要的就是这个效果
yeah, i think that's the point.
除非你想下半辈子都靠出售
unless you want to be selling under-the-counter mags
非法杂志过活
for the rest of your life.
我们不也混到今天了
got us this far.
对 可是你那时在我车子后备箱
yeah, but you were happy selling magazines
卖杂志卖得多开心啊
out of the trunk of my car.
你那个时候也很开心
you were pretty happy then too.
这对我们俩都有好处
this is gonna be great for us.
你会发现的 我们只要让乔伊斯
you'll see. we just got to get joyce
跳出自己的定式思维
out of her own head.
深夜妈咪
♪ late night mama ♪
她喜欢搞事情
♪ she likes to get it on ♪
耶
♪ yeah ♪
她是我的深夜妈咪
♪ and she's my late night mama ♪
她喜欢搞事情
♪ she likes to get it on ♪
她是我的深夜妈咪
♪ oh, she's my late night mama ♪
她喜欢搞事情
♪ she likes to get it on ♪
-这些人是谁  -模特 有潜力的模特
- who are those guys? - models--potential models.
-我们同意了这事不能着急  -我们有了动力
－ we agreed to take our time. - yeah--we've got momentum.
你不能挡住前进的火车
you do not stand in front of a moving train.
我有做大新闻 引人瞩目的大新闻的想法
- i have ideas for big, splashy stories.
-好  -好
- okay, um-- - okay.
我 可以去堕胎诊所当卧底
i--i could go undercover at an abortion clinic,
我可以去倾听被强奸人的第一口述
and i could take firsthand accounts of rape.
你也可以在日落大道上来回走动
you could also walk up and down sunset boulevard,
把我们的想法吼给其他出版商听
shouting our idea into the windows of other publishers.
你对被人挖墙脚怎么这么执念
what is this obsession you have with getting scooped?
光说空话对你的生活有什么好处吗
－ has farting up your own ass gotten you anywhere in life?
显然没有
apparently not.
好了 乔伊斯
okay. joyce, please,
给我几天时间
just give me a couple of days.
我就这么个要求 按我的方法试试
that's all i ask. just try it my way.
好
okay.
身体像是被一道电流击中
"electric flesh-arrows traversing the body.
眼里放射着五彩的光芒
"a rainbow of color strikes the eyelids.
那是高潮的锣鼓
it is the gong of orgasm."
我们在为男性裸体杂志
hey. we're looking for models
找模特
for a male nude magazine.
你们要
you'll be--
要光着屁股 露出大屌
you'll be butt-ass naked, that means your dick.
如果你不乐意 门就在那边
if you got a problem with it, the door's right there.
-开始吧  -太好了
- let's do it. - great.
好 继续
okay. go ahead.
你觉得这不是一种掠夺吗
does this not feel predatory to you?
为什么我们要在
i mean, why do we have to see...
拍照之前看这东西呢
the thing before the photoshoot?
它肯定很好看
i'm sure it's lovely, you know--well,
反正也就那样对吧
i mean, as lovely as they get, right?
长得都差不多 所以
they are all basically the same, so.
不是所有的小弟弟都长一样的 亲爱的
not all wieners are the same, babes.
有些短 有些长 有些粗 有些细
there's shorties, fatties, long ones, flatties.
有些有趣 有些害羞 有些无精打采的 有些精力充沛
playful, shy, jaded, bored.
-你之前有见过男人鸡巴吗  -我当然见过
- you have seen a dick before? - of course i've seen dicks.
见过好多鸡巴
i've seen so many dicks.
我见过两个半
i've seen two and a half.
而且光线很暗
in very dim lighting.
裤子脱了
panties off.
-又短又粗  -这个组合好有趣
- a short fatty. - that's a fun combo.
大鸡吧先生
♪ mr. big stuff ♪
你以为你是谁
♪ who do you think you are? ♪
大鸡吧先生
♪ mr. big stuff ♪
你永远得不到我的爱
♪ you're never gonna get my love ♪
不是因为你穿着
♪ not because you wear ♪
那些高大上的衣服
♪ all those fancy clothes ♪
噢耶
♪ oh, yeah ♪
太好了
oh. great.
对 你现在知道了
♪ oh, yes, you do now ♪
你以为我给不起
♪ do you think i can't afford ♪
你要的爱
♪ to give you my love ♪
噢耶 你以为你比
♪ oh, yeah - you think you're higher ♪
所有的星星都要高大
♪ than every star above ♪
我喜欢他
i like him.
告诉我
♪ tell me ♪
你以为你是谁
♪ who do you think you are? ♪
大鸡吧先生
♪ mr. big stuff ♪
你永远得不到我的爱
♪ you're never gonna get my love ♪
大鸡吧先生
♪ mr. big stuff ♪
你永远不会让我哭泣
♪ you're never gonna make me cry ♪
-不知道 我觉得  -我是谁
- i don't know, i think-- i mean,
你们觉得这个怎么样
what'd you guys think of this one, right?
-我喜欢他  -很可爱
- oh, i loved him. - oh, he's cute.
-他真是很可爱  -对
- and he's a real sweetheart too. - yeah.
-是吧  -他是个可爱的傻帽
- right? - he was an adorable idiot.
他就像人型的金毛猎犬
he was like a golden retriever in human form.
你总是这么挑剔吗
－ are you always this picky?
我们选的这个模特
look, whomever we choose is gonna have
必须要体现我们杂志背后的理念
to sell the philosophy behind the magazine, okay?
如果他缺乏学识
if he's not an intellectual,
那跟《乳娘》有什么区别
then how are we any different than "milky moms"?
乔伊斯 我不想
joyce, i hate to-
抱歉 我把时间看错了
sorry, i read the time wrong.
我以为你们是午夜12点开始的
i thought you guys started at 12:00 a.m.
什么试镜会搞在半夜
what audition starts at midnight?
该死
rats.
我总是把上午下午搞不清楚
i'm always getting my a.m.s and my p.m.s confused.
浪费时间
- oh. - wasting no time.
你在大厅就脱光了吗
did you strip down in our hall?
前台叫我脱的
the receptionist told me to.
我做错了吗
did i do something wrong?
-这样可不好 丽塔  -这种事在我身上
- not cool, rita. - aw, that's happened
发生过无数次了
to me a million times.
做下自我介绍吧
so tell us about yourself.
我叫肖恩
i'm shane.
是个消防员
i'm a fireman.
就这样
is that it?
我在马里布长大
um, i grew up in malibu.
为帕利踢过球 海豚队加油
played football for pali. go dolphins!
好吧 谢谢 我们会电联你的
all right, well, thank you. we will call you.
糟糕
oh. oh, shit.
大家冷静
everyone stay calm.
你们感受的震动是地震
the shaking you're feeling is an earthquake.
谢了你了 我们知道地震什么样的
yes, thank you. we know what an earthquake is.
我们住在洛杉矶
we live in los angeles.
你没事吧 女士
are you okay, ma'am?
没事
yeah.
yeah, um,
我没事
i'm fine.
谢谢
thank you.
只是做我的工作
- just doing my job.
也许我们应该在这里待一会儿
maybe we should stay here just a second,
以免还有余震
in case there's any aftershocks.
好
okay.
没事
that's fine.
乔伊斯有了男朋友 乔伊斯有了男朋友
♪ joyce has a boyfriend, joyce has a boyfriend ♪
他喜欢你 想跟你生孩子
he loves you. he wants to put babies in you.
对
oh, yeah.
瓦萨学院的毕业生要跟我们第一个插页模特滚床单了
vassar's gonna ball our first centerfold.
我没说过他就是我们的插页模特
i never said he was our centerfold.
你这个白人女性
you're a white bitch.
我们想要白人女性读者 因为她们有票子
we want white bitch readers because they have money.
如果你想跟他上
mm. - if you want to fuck him,
其他女人也会这么想的
the other white bitches will too.
我从来没说想跟他上
i never said i want to f him-
你就要在我沙发上射了
ah, you just about creamed my couch.
得了吧
oh, come on!
《金赛性学报告》说 女人饥渴时
the "kinsey reports" says that a woman's vagina
阴道的深度会翻倍
doubles in length when she's horny.
这叫做阴道帐篷
ha! it's called "vaginal tenting".
-宝贝  -好吧 我可能是觉得
- bambi, no. - okay, i may have
他挺理想的 但是不能怪我啊
found him desirable, yes, but it's not my fault.
进化让女人天生会被营救者吸引
evolution has conditioned women to be attracted to rescuers.
要靠我们自己来克服这种动物的欲望
it's up to us to overcome our animal desires--
快叫她闭嘴 那太无聊了
someone please stop her. that is no fun.
-好吧 我可能就是个无趣的人  -你就是
- well, maybe i'm no fun then. - you are.
你对自己有趣的部分感到惧怕
you're just scared of that part of yourself,
因为你觉得这样会显得你软弱
'cause you think it makes you seem weak.
知道吗 人可以是很复杂的动物
you know, you can be more than one thing.
也许对男人来说是这样 女人不能失去重点
uh, maybe for a guy. women cannot lose focus.
好吧 可能是 不管怎样
－ all right, maybe. either way,
这个故事的点子不错
it's a good idea for a story.
这是个好点子 是你刚想出来的吗
mm, that is a good idea. did you just come up with that?
看来我这人也不是简单的动物
i guess i'm more than one thing too.
怎么样
how's that?
-来喝酒  -消防员
- let's drink. - fireman!
消防员 消防员 消防员
all: fireman! fireman! fireman!
-好了 拜  -拜
- okay, bye. - bye!
早上7点了
7:00 a.m. wow.
你有什么需要吗
can i help you with something?
我把你落在我那里的东西
yeah, i was just dropping off some of your stuff
给你送过来
that you left at my place.
想着你可能要准备去上班了呢
thought you'd be getting ready for work by now.
-我要休息一下  -是吗
- took some time off. - did you?
我在跟一个很有声望的出版商
i am developing "the matriarchy awakens"
在研究《女权觉醒》
with a prominent publisher.
那么多晚上
all those nights,
在你房间里忙来忙去为了啥
working away in your room and for what?
就为了你能当帕萨迪纳的黄刊女王吗
so you could be the porn queen of pasadena?
-你怎么知道  -我怎么知道
- how do you know about-- - how do i know?
大家都会知道的 乔伊斯
everybody's gonna know, joyce.
这种事你瞒不住的
this isn't a secret you can keep.
-太低俗了  -总之 这只是
- this is low. - anyway, it's just--
杂志的一小部分 所以
it's a small part of the magazine, so.
你知道麦格雷戈的故事吗
do you know the story of mcgregor?
-谁  -在苏格兰的一家酒吧里
- who? - a drunk starts talking
一个醉汉开始和一个游客交谈
to a tourist in a scottish pub.
他说 你看到那边的码头了吗
he says, "do you see that dock over there?
是我一砖一瓦造的
"i built it myself, stone by stone.
司是他们会叫我码头工人麦格雷戈吗
"but do they call me mcgregor the dock builder?
不会 你看到那边的桥了吗
"no. you see that bridge over there?
那也是我造的
"i built that too.
可是他们会叫我造桥工人麦格雷戈吗
"but do they call me mcgregor the bridge builder?
不会
"no.
但你操了一只羊的话
but you fuck one sheep--"
你真是个混蛋
you're a real jerk, you know that?
而你是个叛徒
－ and you're a sellout.
祝你的杂志好运
good luck with the magazine.
为梦想妥协
compromising your vision.
听起来不太好
it gets a bad rap,
但真的应该这样吗
but should it?
但你知道我会说
you know, i say--
格洛丽亚
gloria?
妥协是为那些
compromise is for those
缺乏斗志的人准备的
who lack the will to fight.
你让我们所有人都成了笑柄
you've made a mockery of us all.
-喂  -宝贝
- hello? - babes!
我们打了一天电话了
we've been calling all day.
拍摄开始了
the photoshoot's a go.
我们6点开始
we start at 6:00.
谁会把拍摄安排在一天之内
who plans a photoshoot in one day?
我们会
we do.
你不觉得这看起来很棒吗
don't you think it looks great?
嘿 里奇 再紧一点怎么样
hey, richie, how'bout a little tighter?
好的
yeah, okay.
这真是拙劣
this is cheesy. and--
抱歉 这太尴尬了
i'm sorry, this is just embarrassing.
这完全没有意义
and it's--this-- it's completely meaningless.
我们应该说点什么
we're supposed to be saying something here.
好了 乔伊斯 来吧 花一分钟享受一下吧
okay, joyce, come on. take a minute and enjoy this.
看看这些人 他们为了实现
look at all these people working hard
你的梦想而努力工作
to make your dream come true.
你以为这是我的梦想吗
you think this is my dream?
我的梦想是一锅美味健康的汤汁
my dream is a pot of delicious, healthy soup,
而你所做的只是往里面加了一小块屎
and what you're doing is adding a tiny little piece of shit
然后搅拌 希望没人会注意到
to it and stirring it in, hoping no one's gonna notice.
-哦 是这样吗  -这对我来说
- oh, is that right? - this is not just
不是一件小事 好吗
some piece of business for me, okay?
这是我毕生的事业
this is my life's work. why should i have
我为什么要为了别人而妥协呢
to compromise that for someone else?
因为你他妈要变得成熟点
because grow the fuck up.
这就是原因
that's why.
你觉得你是在帮我
you think you're doing me a favor?
我已经很成功了
i'm a goddamn success story.
我就是美国梦 我很抱歉地告诉你
i'm the american dream, and i'm sorry to tell you this,
乔伊斯 也许你的杂志没有你想像的那么美好
joyce, but maybe your magazine isn't as good as you think it is--yet.
至少现在还没有
as you think it is--yet.
你凭什么这么说
－ who are you to determine that?
我就是资本
i'm the money.
你的资本太贵了
yeah, well, your money costs too much.
那可太糟糕了 因为只有我
well, that's too bad, 'cause i'm the only one
能看到你的能力
who sees what you can do.
各位 我是要把我的老二挂在消防杆上还是
guys, am i draping my penis over the fire pole or--
什么
what?
嘿 性感女郎
hey, sexy lady.
操死你
fuck you!
我正是这个意思
that's the idea.
哟嚯
yoo-hoo.
我偷了孩子们的篮子 把责任推给了复活节的恶魔
i stole the kids baskets and blamed it on the easter devil.
这是我创造的一个新角色
that's a new character i created.
你不是家里唯一的艺术家
you're not the only artist in the family.
这里
- hmm. - here,
吃点巧克力会感觉好点
chocolate makes it better.
不用 我没事
－ no, i'm fine. - hmm.
你为什么不接我电话
why aren't you answering my calls?
已经好几周了
it's been weeks.
因为我一直在重新思考我的生活
'cause i've been busy rethinking my life.
你最近去过报摊吗
mm, and have you been to a newsstand recently?
研究旅行
you know, a research trip?
不 我受够了这些
nope. i'm done with all that.
我要做格伦做的事
i'm gonna do what glenn does.
坐稳《少女皇后》的位置
sit tight at "teen queen,"
写关于眼线的文章 升职
write about eyeliner, get promoted.
-好吧 如果你  -听着 谢尔
- okay, well, if you-- - look, shell,
我知道你想让我这样
i know that you want this for me,
但我宁愿永远不出版杂志
but i would rather never publish a magazine
也不愿屈服于某人的坏主意
than capitulate to someone's bad idea.
如果这不是个坏主意呢
－ well, what if it isn't a bad idea?
一本全是裸体男人的杂志
－ uh, a magazine full of naked men?
这实在是太愚蠢了
it is deeply, inescapably just silly.
你已经在复活节篮子里找到过了吗
will you look in your easter basket already?
是的
yes. yeah.
打开它 我把这页加了书签
open it up. i bookmarked the page.
终于有一个男性裸体照片插页了
- "at last, a male nude centerfold."
是电视明星伯特·雷诺兹
it's television star burt reynolds.
-像这样的人吗  -乔伊斯 轰动一时
- people like this? - joycie, it's a sensation.
我不知道从什么时候开始 已经40天了
♪ been 40 days since i don't know when ♪
我刚看到她和我最好的朋友在一起
♪ i just saw her with my best friend ♪
你明白我的意思吗
♪ do you know what i mean? ♪
♪ do you know, know what i mean? ♪
我再也不能像以前那样正视他了
i am never gonna be able to look at him the same.
乔伊斯 过来看看这个
joyce, come look at this.
只不过是具躯体而已
it's just a body.
姑娘们 你们在看什么
－ what you looking at, gals?
你应该为了你女朋友这么做 科利
you should do this for your girlfriend, cory.
让她兴奋起来
get her good and hot.
这在工作场合是不合适的
that's inappropriate for the workplace.
欢迎伯特·雷诺兹
would you welcome burt reynolds.
-嗨 约翰  -你好 伯特
- hi, john. - hello, burt.
你站起来我都没认出来
i didn't recognize you standing up.
帮帮我
♪ ooh! help me ♪
真好
- "cat-tastic."
你的街道不错 这不是我想象中的你
your street is lovely. it's not where i pictured you.
是啊 我小时候一直想住在这样的地方
yeah, i always wanted to live in a place like this
现在我住上了
when i was a kid, so now i do.
我想你看过《大都会》吧
i, uh, assume you've seen "cosmo"?
全国都看过《大都会》
the whole country's seen "cosmo."
这是一个骗局
it was a cheat.
他几乎没穿衣服
he was barely even naked,
女人都为之疯狂
and women went crazy for it,
就像你说的那样
just like you said they would.
是的
yep.
这让我想到也许
and it made me think
我们应该再给这家杂志一次机会
that maybe we should give this magazine another shot.
我知道男性色情作品正当时
i know that male erotica is in the zeitgeist now,
但我们仍然走在潮流的前面
but we're still ahead of the curve.
我们可以抢在别人
we could be on the newsstands
之前登上报摊
before anyone else.
是的 你知道的 乔伊斯
yeah. you know, joyce,
问题就在这里
here's the thing.
我随便翻开一本我的杂志
i go to any one of my magazines,
大家都想听我说些什么
and, well, people are dying to hear what i have to say,
但你的表现就像我是个小丑
but you act like i'm some sort of a fucking clown
直到某位曼哈顿编辑
until some fancy manhattan editor
把伯特·雷诺兹拿出来
throws old burt reynolds on a bearskin rug,
然后我才能得到你的认可 对吧
and then i get your stamp of approval, huh?
很长时间里杂志是我的一部分
this magazine has been a part of me for a long time,
我没有意识到让它走进这个世界
and i didn't realize how hard it was gonna be
成为一个活生生的
to let it go out into the world
东西会有多么困难
and become this living, breathing thing.
我还以为你是个俗气的推销员 只会耍些花招
i thought you were a tacky salesman with a cheap gimmick.
你确实是这种人
and you kind of are,
但你知道一些我正在琢磨的事
but you do know something that i'm just figuring out.
一本杂志必须让你有某种感觉
that a magazine has--it's got to make you feel something,
看到一个裸体的男人会让女人产生这种感觉
and seeing a naked guy does that to women,
不管她们是好奇 兴奋
whether they are curious or turned on
还是只是想嘲笑他
or just want to laugh at him,
这是一种让女人
it's the ability to look
感到强大的能力
makes a woman feel powerful.
这就是我们杂志的宗旨
that's what our magazine is all about.
或者 你知道 如果
or, you know, it could be if...
你再给我一次机会
you give me one more chance.
我不知道 乔伊斯 我得
i don't know, joyce. i'll have to, uh--
我得好好考虑一下
i'll have to think about it.
好吧 做决定不要太久 道格
all right, well, don't fart up your ass for too long, doug.
我有个插页的好主意
i have a killer idea for a centerfold.
噢 不错
oh, yes.
这可是个好东西
that's hot stuff right there.
好了 女士们 我无聊了 给我更多
okay, ladies, i'm bored. give me more.
-污起来  -看这里 宝贝
- be dirty. - look over here, baby!
嘿 让我们看看你的老二
hey! show us your dick!
女人也可以这么烈的啊
jeez. being a woman's intense.
-是啊  -快给我们
- yeah! - give it to us.
不错 乔伊斯
not bad, joyce.
你知道吗 我得感谢你的插页
you know, i got to hand it to you with this centerfold.
你从帽子里变出了一只兔子
you pulled a rabbit out of a hat.
-谢谢你  -你进步得很快
- thank you. - you've come a long way fast.
生活的收缩或扩张与一个人的勇气成正比
"life shrinks or expands in proportion to one's courage.
生命是 是一个形成的过程
life is--" - "is a process of becoming."
你读过那本书啊
you read the books?
是你让我这么做的 那又怎样 我喜欢他们
you asked me to, so what? i liked'em.
那个阿娜伊斯·宁 她说话真有一套
she's got a way with words, that anais nin.
发音是阿内斯·宁
it's pronounced "anays neen."
你是在逗我吗
are you kidding me right now?
-我不知道我为什么这么做  -好的
- i don't know why i do it. - okay.
-好吧 乔伊斯 有个大问题  -嗯
- all right, joyce, big question. - yeah.
我们要怎么取标题
what are we gonna do about a title?
什么杂志 什么都没有
what, of the magazine? nothing.
《女权觉醒》有什么问题吗
what's wrong with "the matriarchy awakens"?
-这不太行  -恶心
- it's poon poison. - gross.
小妞们听到了 马上就干了
chicks hear it, they dry right up.
我们需要的
what we need
是一个性感的标题
is a wet pussy title.
一个湿润女性阴户的标题
a wet pussy title?
山顶上的女神
♪ a goddess on a mountain top ♪
闪烁如银亮的火焰
♪ was burning like a silver flame ♪
绝顶美貌与无上的爱情
♪ the summit of beauty and love ♪
维纳斯就是她的名字
♪ and venus was her name ♪
她有魔力
♪ she's got it ♪
宝贝 是的 她有魔力
♪ yeah, baby, she's got it ♪
我是你的维纳斯 我能点燃你的爱火
♪ well, i'm your venus, i'm your fire ♪
满足你的无限渴望
♪ at your desire ♪
我是你的维纳斯 我能点燃你的爱火
♪ well, i'm your venus, i'm your fire ♪
满足你的无限渴望
♪ at your desire ♪
提防她水晶般的双眼
♪ her weapons were her crystal eyes ♪
足够让每个男人疯狂
♪ making every man mad ♪
如黑夜般邪气
♪ black as the dark night she was ♪
她的魔力无人拥有
♪ got what no one else had, wow ♪
她有魔力
♪ she's got it ♪
是的 宝贝 她有魔力
♪ yeah, baby, she's got it♪
我是你的维纳斯 我能点燃你的爱火
♪ well, i'm your venus, i'm your fire ♪
满足你的无限渴望
♪ at your desire ♪
我是你的维纳斯 我能点燃你的爱火
♪ well, i'm your venus, i'm your fire ♪
满足你的无限渴望
♪ at your desire ♪
获取更多免费资源微信小程序【盘子巴士】